studystack.com 2018-10-01

# Study Stack - Privacy

The following statement outlines StudyStack's policies and principles regarding online privacy. StudyStack is committed to protecting the privacy of its users. 

StudyStack reserves the right to modify this policy statement at any time without notice. As such, and since we want to always make certain that our privacy policy is clearly understood, we recommend that you review this Privacy Statement periodically to note any changes that may have occurred. Please forward any comments you may have regarding this policy to us at [privacy@studystack.com](mailto:privacy@studystack.com). 

## Personally Identifiable Information (PII)

When a user signs up to join StudyStack, StudyStack will store the e-mail address entered into our database of users. StudyStack will not sell your email address to any other company. However, by providing your email address, StudyStack will be able to contact you if necessary with information about the StudyStack web site. Your email address is primarily used for resetting your password if you ever forget it.

The only time StudyStack requests a name to be entered is if a user upgrades to StudyStack's PRO plan. This Upgrade page is not accessible to accounts that registerd as being 12 or younger. The information entered while subscribing to the PRO plan is not sent to studystack's servers but is transmitted to stripe.com for payment processing.

StudyStack reserves the right to collect information regarding who entered what data. This allows StudyStack to notify the individual who entered a certain piece of information if it suspects that the information is incorrect. If a copyright holder claims that information you entered infringes on their copyright, StudyStack may share your email address with them. 

If you use facebook to connect to studystack, your name and facebook profile picture will be displayed on flashcard pages that you create. If you do not want this data displayed, do not use facebook to connect to studystack. 

StudyStack occasionally provides a support feature that allows users to interact with StudyStack using a chat session. This feature is only available to users that have logged in and who have indicated that they are over the age of 13. 

## Non-Personally Identifiable Information (Non-PII)

While you use the StudyStack web site, StudyStack may collect information such as what pages with-in the StudyStack web site you visited. This information will only be used by StudyStack to improve the web site.

**Data that you enter for your flashcards will be displayed publicly. Do not include personal information in your flashcards that you want to remain private!**

We allow third-party companies to collect certain information when you visit our web site. These companies may utilize cookies, pixels or other technologies to collect and use both personally identifiable information (e.g., your name, phone number, physical or electronic address) and non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit the websites of the Digital Advertising Alliance at www.aboutads.info or Networking Advertising Initiative at www.networkadvertising.org/choices. 

## Advertisements

To allow StudyStack to remain a free website, StudyStack displays advertisements on its pages. Alternatively, you may upgrade to our PRO plan that does not display ads. We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. Many of the ads displayed are from Google's AdSense advertising network. These ads may allow Google to know that you have visited the StudyStack web site. This information helps Google to display "interest-based" ads that should interest you more. If you prefer not to participate in interest-based advertising, you may [opt out of this program at google.com.](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html)

Clicking on advertisements will redirect you to the web page of the advertiser. The StudyStack privacy statement does not apply to the advertiser's website.

## Contacting Us

If you have particular concerns about this privacy statement, please contact [privacy@studystack.com](mailto:privacy@studystack.com)

John Weidner  
13025 SW 47th ST  
Mustang, OK 73064

Phone: 405 806 0070
